compactappliance.com 2002-02-08

# Privacy & Security

CompactAppliance.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.  By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, CompactAppliance.com has agreed to notify you of:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the web site.

  2. The organization collecting the information.

  3. How the information is used.

  4. With whom the information may be shared.

  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information.

  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under CompactAppliance.com control.

  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Jason Roussos, Internet Content Manager, by email at [roussos@compactappliance.com](mailto:roussos@compactappliance.com).  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the ["TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process."](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog_intro.html)

**Your Personal Information  
**We at compactAppliance.com recognize your right to privacy and are committed to protecting your privacy.  We use the information that we collect on our site to provide you with a superior shopping experience.  When you order, we will ask for information that will ensure that your order is processed in an accurate, secure, and timely manner.  Information we ask for includes your name, e-mail address, contact phone number, mailing and billing address, and credit card number and expiration date.  In fulfilling your order, we only share your personal information with outside parties to the extent necessary to fulfill your order.  We may also run contests on our web site in which we ask visitors for contact information that includes name, address, and e-mail address.  This information is used to contact contestants if they should win.  We will use your email to periodically send you our e-mail newsletter that contains special offers and updates about our products and services.  You may opt-out of receiving these emails and you may modify your contact information at any time.  

You will receive administrative emails regarding your order that cannot be opt-ed out of.  The first email you receive will serve as receipt of your order.  The information included in this email consists of sales price, order number, and shipping information.  You will receive a second email when your order ships.  This will contain all tracking information so that you will be able to locate the status of your order at any time. 

We protect your account information against unauthorized access or release.  We will not give, sell, rent, or loan any identifiable personal information to any third party unless you have authorized us or we are legally required to do so. **Cookies  
**To personalize your experience at CompactAppliance.com, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie.  Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive.  We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.  By disabling cookies you will not be able to use the shopping cart feature on the CompactAppliance.com web site. **Log Files  
**Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.  We use IP addresses, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to any personal, identifiable information.

 **Live Chat Help  
** CompactAppliance.com incorporates a live chat option on its website.  A third party service provider powers the chat functionality.  Information obtained through this order form of communication may not be used or shared with the third party  hosting the software. **Links to/from Other Sites  
**To enhance your shopping experience, the CompactAppliance.com site may have links to other sites on the internet that are owned by third party vendors and other third parties (External Sites), or you may come to CompactAppliance.com from a link from an external site.  The other web sites will have their own rules on privacy that you should review.  CompactAppliance.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of external sites.

**Correcting, Updating, Deactivating  
** There are several ways to update information you have provided CompactAppliance.com:

  * Email [info@compactappliance.com](mailto:info@compactappliance.com) to update or change any information you may have provided us.
  * Email [optout@compactappliance.com](mailto:optout@compactappliance.com) to be removed from our newsletter
  * Call toll free at 800 297-6076
  * You may also respond to the email with "Remove" or "Unsubscribe" in the subject line to be removed from any future newsletters.

**Sweepstakes  
** CompactAppliance.com offers sweepstakes on its web site.  Any information collected in registering for these sweepstakes is used to contact individuals should they win.  We will also use your email address to send you a newsletter containing information on specials and events.  You may opt-out of receiving notices by indicating "Remove" or "Unsubscribe" in the subject line.

**Security  
**This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information.  To protect your privacy, CompactAppliance.com has teamed up with Yahoo!Store to provide our shopping cart technology.  Our shopping cart incorporates industry-standard secure server software (Secure Socket Layers) into sensitive sections of our store.  All online transactions at CompactAppliance.com are handled using this encryption technology.  When you enter your credit card number into the order form, it is transmitted across the internet in an  encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets out.  For added security, we also encrypt the credit card number when it is stored on disk.Paymentech Services, a state-of-the-art credit card verification service, keeps CompactAppliance.com's transactions secure by encrypting all of your personal information while validating the transaction.  We use RSA encryption technology to scramble your data so that it would be virtually impossible to break into.There are two ways to make sure you are browsing secure pages.  Both Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator indicate secure modes with a symbol - the image of a closed padlock.  You will know the information is protected if the closed-lock symbol pops into view in the lower right or left-hand corner of your screen while you are checking it out.  You can also verify secure pages by checking the address, or URL, listed on the scroll bar.  If you spot an "s"after the "http" at the beginning of the address, you know that you're browsing in a secure environment. **Federal Law Limits Your Liability**  
Federal law limits an individual's liability if their credit card information should ever fall into the wrong hands.  Under the Fair Credit Billing Act of 1975, you may dispute the charges on your account with your credit card company and temporarily withhold payment while they investigate the situation.  Even if your creditor disagrees that unauthorized purchases were made, you're generally only liable for the first $50 in fraudulent charges. **Notification of Changes  
**If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under any circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  However, if you have opted out of communication with the site then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner.  Users will have a choice whether or not we use their information in this different manner.  We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

   Our Mission  
   Privacy Policy  
   FAQ  
   Hours of Operation  
   Testimonials  
   How to Shop

   Order Status  
   Payment  
   Shipping  
   Damages  
   Extended Warranty  
   Return Policy  
   Cancellation Policy  
   Placing an Order
